gameshop-international.com 2017-03-02

# Download Free Full PC Games

**GAMESHOP-INTERNATIONAL.COM PRIVACY POLICY  
  
**

_This document was last updated 10.06.2013.  
_

Eurotronic Arts d.o.o. and its subsidiary GameShop-International.com are committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how Eurotronic Arts d.o.o. (owner of GameShop-International.com site) collects and utilizes your personal information when you use our products and services.  

**  
WHY DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
**  
Eurotronic Arts d.o.o. collects personal information to improve the manner by which we operate and offer our products and services, communicate with you about those products and services, and provide effective, timely customer support when needed. We will never rent or sell any of the personally-identifiable information we collect from you to third parties, and will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent, unless such sharing is necessary for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.  

**  
WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?   
**  
Information that you provide when accessing or using products or services associated may include: name and email address; billing information; information concerning software downloaded, products and content purchased, accessed, downloaded location information (such as zip code or postal code and country); computer configuration (such as operating system, connection speed, and peripherals); the IP Internet (IP) address and URL of the Website that sent you to GameShop-International.com page; these devices); demographic information provided by you. We will not sell, rent or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as set forth below.  

**  
HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?  
**  
Eurotronic Arts d.o.o. understands that it is a privilege to have you as a customer and is committed to protecting your personal information. We use the following controls to protect your personal information:  

Use of secure connections using SSL to safeguard information when transmitted from your Web browser to GameShop-International.com;

Use of security controls to restrict access to databases housing personally identifying information

Use of encryption for sensitive personal information, such as credit card numbers

Restrict employee access to databases containing personal information and impose confidentiality requirements upon employees who do; and

Bind subcontractors with contractual, technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
**  
GameShop-International.com uses your personal information to:

Deliver to you and and bill you for products and services, and to communicate with you. This may include verifying authorization of credit card usage before any purchase of products.  

**WHEN AND HOW DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?  
**  
GameShop-International.com does not sell, rent, or share your personal information to a third party unless you consent to provide such information to a third party partner or content service.  

**  
E-MAIL FROM GAMESHOP-INTERNATIONAL.COM  
**  
Generally, we send e-mail to you about our products, content and special offers.  

**  
SECURITY OF PERSONAL AND PAYMENT INFORMATION  
**  
**USE OF COOKIES  
**  
Like other major Websites, we use cookies to provide you with a tailored experience when visiting our Websites and using our products. We also use cookies to understand traffic patterns on GameShop-International.com Website. We treat any personal information that may be contained in cookies with the same level of confidentiality as other information you provide to us.

GameShop-International.com does not require that you accept cookies, however, some functionality on our Website, our product purchase check-out process, and products and services may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

**PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT**

Our website uses cookies. Cookies are small files downloaded to your computer. So that we can recognize you when you return to our site.

We use the following cookies:

Cookie "ASPSESSIONIDAASRSCST" - Is a system cookie that takes care of your session on our website and it is also necessary for the operation of our website.

Cookies "_utm *" and "is_unique" -These cookies are used by analytical tools Google Analitycs and StatsCounter that allow us to count and analysis website visitors.

Cookie "DEL-local" - Is a cookie from Digicert who provides SSL secure connection.

Information collected through cookies will not be disclosed to third parties.

If you do not want to store cookies to your device, you can change the settings here.

 **

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

**

We frequently revise this Privacy Policy to keep it up to date.

 **

CONTACT US ABOUT PRIVACY

**

If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our products or services or would like to make a suggestion, please contact:

**  
Eurotronic Arts d.o.o.  
Klopciceva ulica 4  
SI- 1000 Ljubljana  
Slovenia, Europe  
**
